YOHANNES NABABAN

UI/UX DESIGNER

It is happy to evaluate and redesign a website or application in order to produce a product that has the usability, ease and satisfaction of a good user experience. Committed to making a big impact on the progress of the company I work for.



- Komplek IAKN, Jalan Raya Balige Km 11, Jambatan Bosi, Desa Pagarbatu, Silangkitang
- yohannesn24.yn@gmail.com
- in LinkedIn: Yohannes Nababan
- O Instagram: nessnbn

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

Del Institute of Techonology

BACHELOR OF INFORMATIC 2016

• Maintained a 3.18 GPA all 8 semesters

CERTIFICATIONS

UI Design Specialization

2020

COURSERA

Human Interaction Computer-HCI

2020

INTERACTION DESIGN FOUNDATION



SPECIALIZATIONS

- User Experience Designer
- User Interface Designer
- Automation Testing
- Manual Testing
- Interaction Design
- Usability Testing
- Heuristic Evaluation

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Tester Internship

PT. TELKOM INDONESIA
JUNE 2019 TO AGUSTUS 2019

- Manual Testing of several websites belonging to Telkom Indonesia
- Automation testing of several websites belonging to Telkom Indonesia using Katalon Studio
- Performance Testing of several websites belonging to Telkom Indonesia using Jmeter

ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCE

Member of Del Student Choir

DEL INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY 2016 - 2018

Member of Communication and Information Division

HIMPUNAN MAHASISWA TEKNIK INFORMATIKA 2017 - 2018

Voluntary at Toba Enterpreneurship Festival

DEL INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY 2017 - 2018